filixy.com 2014-11-13

# Privacy Policy - Filixy Directory

Top » Privacy Policy

**Information Collection and Use**

Flixy is the sole owner of the information collected on filixy.com We collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

During the Flixy Submit service, we require information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

**Information Use**

We store information that we collect through log files, and via the information provided during the Flixy Submit service, to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their characteristics. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the user experience. We DO NOT share your profile with other third parties.

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Communications**

Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, or special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections.

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications - these communications are not promotional in nature. 

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user’s wishes.

**Sharing**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This information includes: page views, unique visitors, browsers, and additional broad demographical data. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

Flixy shares Web site usage information about users with reputable third party advertisers for the purpose of targeting our advertisements. Be advised that tough we make every effort to accept only reputable advertisers, that we cannot held responsible for the Privacy Policies of any advertiser, promotional link, sponsor, or other third party. Please make sure to check the individual Privacy Policy of any third party site that you visit.

**Instances in which Flixy Will Share Users' Personal Information**

We use an outside credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

In the event Flixy goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of their personal information. If as a result of the business transition, the users’ personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection they will be given choice consistent with our notification of changes section.

**Links**

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Flixy, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our financial department or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees are encouraged to use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Our employees are reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, behind a locked cage, in a locked facility.

**Modifying Personal Information**

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct or update users’ personally identifiable information.

**Notice of Change**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. However, if users have opted out of all communication with the site, or deleted/deactivated their account, then they will not be contacted, nor will their personal information be used in this new manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our Web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post a notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices.
